Finding Aid for the USA for Africa Records LSC.1669
UCLA Library Special Collections
- RD II Rejected Proposals
  - Sudan (Box 149, Box 150, Box 151, Box 152)
    - Control of trachoma - 386. (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - Agricultural marketing & credit co-operative - 397. (Box 151, Folder 22)
    - Agricultural training center (YATC) - 398. (Box 151, Folder 23)
    - Women's Health Initiative Nile river project - 418. (Box 151, Folder 24)
    - Medical / nutritional support - 424. (Box 151, Folder 25)
    - Relief of Tigray - 451. (Box 151, Folder 26)
    - Food processing - technologies - 452. (Box 151, Folder 27)
    - Water resources - 533. (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Nutrition education - 546. (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Eritrean Red Cross - 702. (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Sudan Council of Voluntary Agencies (SCOVA) - 717. (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Tigray relief - 325. (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Swaziland - Horticultural scheme - 522. (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Tanzania - Water supply - Hospitals - 502. (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Uganda (Box 152, Folder 8-13)
    - Emergency aid - West Nile bank - 444. (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Emergency storage facilities - 445. (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Warehouses - 446. (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Emergency - National immunization project - 568. (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Uganda rural development project - 269 ["missing proposal"]. (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Village water system - 503. (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Zambia - Health / water / livestock - 391. (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Zimbabwe (Box 152, Folder 15-18)
    - Catholic Development Commission (CADEC) support - 504. (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Training for displaced persons - 532. (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Mozambican refugees - 287. (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Child survival - 700. (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Partnership for progress. (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Pan-African development Corporation. (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Program for Appropriate Technology in Health (PATH). (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - Physician inquiries. (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - P.R.I.C.O.R. (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - P.R.I.T.E.C.H. (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Project Concern International. (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - Radda Barnen. (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - St. Joseph's hospital & medical center. (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - Rehabilitation International. (Box 152, Folder 28)
  - Red Cross. (Box 152, Folder 29)
  - Save the Children. (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - SAS - Service antiacridon du Sahel. (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - SMARTMED. (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Somalia. (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Unitarian Universalist Service. (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Simmonds, Stephane. (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Sister Cities International. (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Linda Shreyer Productions. (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Senegal. (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Shabab el Bina. (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - San Diego State University. (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Sudan. (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Sudanese associations. (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Sudan council of churches. (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Svenska Sudanska Foereningen. (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Terra-Genesis / Terres des Hommes. (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Tesfa village Incorporated. (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Trickle-Up. (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Tufts University. (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Tulane. (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Third World medical research foundation. (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Thrasher foundation. (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - TransAfrica. (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - United Nations Decade for women conference. (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees. (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - UGVO. (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) - Senegal. (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - U.N.I.C.E.F. (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - U.N.I.C.E.F. - Niger. (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - University of Pennsylvania. (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - University of Rochester [empty]. (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - University of Washington. (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - University of Wisconsin. (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Utica College. (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - University of Buffalo. (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - University of California, Davis. (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - UCLA. (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - University of California, San Francisco. (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - University of Miami [empty]. (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - University of North Carolina. (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - U.S. policy. (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - U.U.S.C. (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - University of Arizona. (Box 154, Folder 24)
  - United Nations Emergency office. (Box 154, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Council for International Business. (Box 154, Folder 26)
  - U.S.A. for Africa - Individual inquiries - Africa section. (Box 154, Folder 27)
  - U.S.A. for Africa project report summary-1986-1987 (?). (Box 154, Folder 28)
  - UNWRA. (Box 154, Folder 29)
  - U.S.A. for Africa project requests. (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Visions of peace. (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Warner Lambert Company. (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Washington office for Africa. (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - WHO. (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - WHO - Expanded prog. on immunity. (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - WHO - Mutalik. (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Well start. (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Woman pioneer. (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Women and the law - Botswana. (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Woodrow Wilson school. (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - World Concern. (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - World University Service of Canada. (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - World Vision. (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - World Federation of Public Health Associations [empty]. (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - WHO. (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - World Education. (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - World Neighbors. (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - World Research Foundation. (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - WUSC. (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Yale University. (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Vanderbuilt University. (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Viscom International. (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Westside cluster of centers & settlements. (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - "Catholic Relief Services" to "Hospital sans frontieres" - P2&3 to P12. (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - "Int'l League of the Red Cross" to "Medicins sans frontieres" - P13 to P17. (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - "Mercy Corps International" to "World Neighbors" - P18&19 to P32. (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - American medical training (Box 157, Box 158)
    - AMSA full proposal. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - International exchange medical training. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Johns Hopkins. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - University of Arizona. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - University of Washington. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Yale University. (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Reference copies for January review (Box 158, Folder 6-12)
    - Conference proposals. (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Surgical Aid to the Children of the World. (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Dennis Carlson. (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Family Health International. (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - U.N.I.C.E.F. - Niger. (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - University of Rochester. (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Warner Lambert. (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Full proposals, January 1987 (Box 159, Folder 1-9)
    - Family Health International. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Proposals pending. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Airlift: Mozambique - 06202. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Addis Ababa / Case West. (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - ADES - Nouni - Lo. (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - American Joint Jewish Distribution Committee. (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - AMREF. (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - CARE. (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - CARE - Sudan. (Box 159, Folder 9)
- United Nations Correspondence / Memos
  - Unfoldered materials. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Non-Health curr. act. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Ethiopia. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Lere Bridge - Chad. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Chad. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mali. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Emergency assistance: reporting. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Chad R/D. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Burkina Faso. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Burkino Faso R/D. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Ethiopia: United Nations Projects. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - US/AF Emergency - General. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Mali. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Niger. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Mozambique R/D. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Sudan. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Mozambique. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Niger. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Sudan. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Senegal. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - U.S.A. AF., July/August, no year (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Recon/Develop Coord. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - U.S.A. for Africa: Emergency., December 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Action., October/November, no year (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. for Africa., May/June 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Medical Task Force guidelines. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - U.S.A. for Africa. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - African Society for Equal Opportunities Handicapped. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Burkina Faso. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ethiopia Health. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Health Project Lists [empty]. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Angola. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - January 29 Meeting. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - March 26 meeting. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Medical Task Force: Current. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - April 16 meeting with Redlener. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Sudan. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Niger. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mozambique. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mauritania [empty]. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Mali. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Rapid-response Fund requests. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Recon/Develop: Current. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Live-Aid concerts. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Second round submissions. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - U.S.A. for Africa International Act meeting., July 9, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Meeting with K. Jenden., November 27, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - InterAction/U.S.A. for Africa. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Interaction Subcommittee meeting., April 26, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Interaction/U.S.A. for Africa. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Program Review Board. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Program Review Board June 29-30. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Program Review Board. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - U.S.A. for Africa General. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - U.S.A. for Africa: Projects. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - U.S.A. for Africa: Current. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Sudan. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Health. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. for Africa "New Round." (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Recovery/Development. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Angola. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Mali. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Chad. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ethiopia. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Senegal. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Mozambique. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Burkina Faso. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Niger. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Emerg (to September). (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - U.S.A. for Africa: Current. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Mozambique flight. (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Live Aid (U.S.). (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Band Aid/Live Aid. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - BAT/LAF., Fall/Winter 1985/86 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Band Aid/Live Aid. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - U.S.A. for Africa MTF., September 8, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Unlabelled. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Recovery/Development Current. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - M.T.F. Action. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Unlabelled folder. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. for Africa BAT/LAF Action. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation: Action. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Mozambique Flight. (Box 27, Folder 1)
- WATW Africa Tapes
  - Miscellaneous proposals. (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Lion Share, February 23, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 1-3)
    - Reels 1-3., (3 reels tied [3/4"]) (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Reels 4-6., (3 reels tied [3/4"]) (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Reel 7., ([3/4"]) (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Local Heroes Global Change, [VHS] (Box 171, Folder 4-7)
    - Program 1: "With Our Own Eyes." (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Program 2: "Against the Odds." (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Program 3: "Power to Change." (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Program 4: "The Global Connection." (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Lion Share, February 23, 1986 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Reel 7., [3/4"] (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Reels 4-6., (3 reels tied [3/4"]) (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - "We Are The World" - U.S.A. for Africa - Final version., [3/4"] (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Ethiopia - 50 years - English., [VHS] (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Read - A - Vision., [VHS] (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Dealing with Interdependence., November 1987; [VHS] (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Campaign to End Hunger., [VHS] (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Coke "We are the World" - Grandfather - Demo., February 26, 1986; [3/4"] (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - "We are the World" - U.S.A. for Africa., February 19, 1986; (2 copies [3/4"]) (Box 173, Folder 2-3)
  - Overseas Education Fund (OEF) - Video letter exchange - Knoxville to Nigeria., May 1989; [VHS] (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - CBS This Morning - "Mozambique.", January 16-18, 1990; [VHS] (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Famine - Ethiopia., [VHS] (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Overseas Education Fund (OEF) - Video letter exchange - Chicago to Mbao II., October 1989; [VHS] (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - American Red Cross - Africa case statement., [3/4"] (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - UNICEF DCI - "African information conference 1984.", [3/4"] (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Black Angus - "We are the World" - "Stop the Noise.", [3/4"] (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Education Fund (OEF) - Video letter exchanges., 1989; [VHS] (Box 174, Folder 4-7)
    - Ngodiba to Knoxville II., November 1989 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Ngodiba to Knoxville II., November 1989 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Knoxville to Ngodiba., August 1989 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Presentation and playback in Ngodiba., June 1989 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - "We are the World: A Year of Giving" - Final cut - Unsweetened., November 11, 1985; [3/4"] (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Steymed generators (1)., [Beta] (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Plane POV clouds 2017T., [3/4"] (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - "We are the World" - U.S.A. for Africa., [VHS] (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Destabilizing Angola: South Africa's war & U.S. policy., [VHS] (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Overseas Education Fund (OEF) - Video letter exchange - Chicago to Mbao., May 1989; [VHS] (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Overseas Education Fund (OEF) - Video letter exchange - Ngodiba to Knoxville., June 1989; [VHS] (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Exerpts from JFK's inaugural address., [3/4"] (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Star Search finals., 1986; [3/4"] (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Robert Serect - Old., [3/4"] (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Care: A Bigger Package for a Smaller World., [VHS] (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Synanon (SDN) compilation tape., [Beta] (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Jordan - Off line., [Beta] (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - "Harry Belafonte - U.S.A. for Africa" - NBC-TV / Network Los Angeles., [VHS] (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - David Talisman - "The Way of Love.", [3/4"] (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - News briefs dubbed from VHS - Bad quality., [Beta] (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Tom's Liberty weekend footage., [3/4"] (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Education Fund (OEF) - Video letter exchange - Mbao to Chicago., June 1989; [VHS] (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Third World challenge to U.S. policy., [VHS] (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - ABC 20/20 - "Children of Terror / Mozambican Civil War.", March 2, 1990; [VHS] (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Refugee camp - U.S.A. for Africa. (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Representative Udall., May 1, 1986; [Beta] (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Susanne's work tape., [Beta] (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - South Africa Now - Mozambique coverage highlights., [VHS] (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - "Ethiopia / U.S.A. for Africa" - NBC Today show / Network Los Angeles., [VHS] (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Show no.8741 - Ethiopia., [VHS] (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Zambia - World Bank - Children's express - CE News Magazine (PBS)., [VHS] (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - "The First Shipment from U.S.A. for Africa Arrives in Ethiopia" - Los Angeles coverage - Master., [3/4"] (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - "U.S.A. for Africa" - CBS West 57th Street., [3/4"] (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - "We are the World" - U.S.A. for Africa., January 26, 1989; [3/4"] (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - "Famine in Ethiopia" - NBC Today show., [VHS] (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - South Africa Now / Mozambique coverage highlights - Supported by U.S.A. for Africa., [VHS] (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Dealing with Interdependence: The U.S. & the Third World., November 1987; [VHS] (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - "Farm Crisis: The Black Experience.", [VHS] (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - "We are the World" - U.S.A. for Africa., April 19, 1989; [3/4"] (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - U.S.A. for Africa - Visit to Africa., June 1985; [3/4"] (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Bob Geldof - CBS 60 Minutes., [3/4"] (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Boston News., [3/4"] (Box 180, Folder 4-5)
  - Campus Network - Season 2., [3/4"] (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Apple Computer / Handset: "Training session.", [Beta] (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Hands Across America Commercial / Video., [Beta] (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Synanon Distribution Network. (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - "The Empty Space"; "Rolling Stones Trailer"; "New Guinea exerpts"; "20/20.", [VHS] (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Miske-En - The Destitute., [Beta] (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - "We Are The World.", [Reel-to-reel] (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Gerry Feil's Africa film., 1969-70; [VHS] (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Unlabelled., [VHS] (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - "We Are The World" (in Arabic)., [Tape cassette] (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - "Africa News.", [Tape cassette] (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - "A.F.R.I.C.A.", [VHS] (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Project 269, [Beta and Beta 1] (Box 198, Box 199, Box 200, Box 201)
    - Reel 400, part 1. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 1., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Reel 400, part 2. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 1., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Reel 401, part 1. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 2., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Reel 401, part 2. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 2., [3/4/"] (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Reel 402, part 1. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 3., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Reel 402, part 2. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 3., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Reel 403, part 1. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 4., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Reel 403, part 2. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 4., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Reel 404, part 1. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 5., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Reel 404, part 2. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 5., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Reel 405, part 1. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 6., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Reel 405, part 2. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 6., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Reel 406, part 1. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 7., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Reel 406, part 2. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 7., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Reel 407, part 1. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 9., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Reel 407, part 2. Mo Amin: Ethiopia 9., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Reel 409. Mo Amin: Sudan 1., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - S-2 - reel 410. Mo Amin: Sudan 2., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - S-3 - reel 411, part 1. Mo Amin: Sudan 3., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 19)
    - S-3 - reel 411, part 2. Mo Amin: Sudan 3., [3/4"] (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - Reel 412. Mo Amin: Sudan 5., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Reel 413. Mo Amin: Sudan 6., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Reel 414. Mo Amin: Sudan 7., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Reel 415. Mo Amin: Sudan 8., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Reel 416, part 1. Mo Amin: Sudan 9., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Reel 416, part 2. Mo Amin: Sudan 9., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Reel 417, part 1. Mo Amin: Sudan 10., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Reel 417, part 2. Mo Amin: Sudan 10., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Reel 419. Mo Amin: Tanzania 5., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Reel 420. Mo Amin: Tanzania 6., [3/4"] (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Reel 423. (Box 199, Folder 11)
      (Henninger Video) African Calvary.
    - Reel 423 "African Calvary." (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Reel 520. (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Reels 14-15, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Reels 16-17, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Reels 18-19, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Reels 20-21, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Reels 22-23, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Reels 24-25, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Reels 26-27, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Reels 28-29, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Reels 30-31, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Reels 32-33, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Reels 34-35, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Reels 36-37, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Reels 38-39, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Reels 48-49, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Reels 50-51, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Reel 52, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Reels 53-54, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Reels 79-80, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Reels 82-83, Burn-In Dub., [Beta 1] (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Tape 108, Burn-In. (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - U.N.I.C.E.F. (Box 201, Folder 2-3)
    - "The African Emergency Situation" - English version., [3/4"] (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - "Ethiopia Emergency.", [3/4"] (Box 201, Folder 3)
- W.I.D. Rejects
  - Groupements "Naam" du Yatenga. (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - W.I.D. miscellaneous. (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Support Association for Local Development Initiatives (ASSAILD) - WD906. (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - C.O.D.E.L. - Tree farming (Botswana) - WD907. (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - C.O.D.E.L. - development & training for women (Swaziland) - WD908. (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Babiker Badri Scientific Association for Women Studies - WD 909. (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Centre for Development and Population Activities (CEDPA) - Senegal / Mali - W.I.D. 910. (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Centre for Development and Population Activities (CEDPA) / Mali - information. (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Oxfam/U.S. - WD911. (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Grassroots, International - WD913. (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - World education - WD915. (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - S.F.C.A. - WD916. (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - P.A.I.D. - ESA - Correspondence - 16901. (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - International Center for Research on Women - WID919. (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Africa Now - WD920. (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Al Sudaniya - WD922. (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - National Committee for Water, Child & Health - WD923. (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - National Council of Negro Women / A.A.W.O.R.D. (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - I.A.C. - WD925. (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - C.F.D.A.P. / Ministry of Health - WD926. (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Ethiopian Gemini Trust - WD928. (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - P.A.C.T. - WD930. (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - F.I.H. - WD932. (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Tanzania Media Women Association - WD933. (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Tanzania Media Women Association - information. (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Bethlehem Training Center - WD936. (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - African Research & Communication, Incorporated. (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - F.A.F.S. - WD941. (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Save the Children - WID942. (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Ministry of Social Affairs - WD944. (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Dar el Barka Project - WD946. (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Union Nationale des Femmes de Djibouti - WID939. (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Sahel Solidairty - WD940. (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (FAO) - Proposal summary & sample proposal - 03WD947-951. (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Belle Service co-operative - Project summary - 03WD947. (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Women in Anchucho - Project summary - 03WD948. (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Duro Service co-operative - Project summary - 03WD949. (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Duza Yeza Service co-operative - Project summary - 03WD950. (Box 133, Folder 17)